Minh Quoc Tran

JUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Binh Tan District, Ho Chi Minh City

【 (+84) 706 863 720 | ■ ts4blader@gmail.com | ☑ github.com/ts4blader | in linkedin.com/in/tmquoc

Summary

Creative Front-End Developer offering 2+ years of experience providing high-impact web solutions for diverse industry organizations. Skilled in designing, developing multiple web-based applications incorporating a range of technologies. Aspiring to combine a broad background with strong technical skills to excel as a Front-End Developer. Creative

Skills

Programming Javascript(Typescript).

Frameworks/Libs ReactJS, NextJS, Redux, SASS, LESS, CSS Module, Ant Design, Storybooks, TailwindCSS, Redis, Prisma, NodeJS.

Miscellaneous Linux, Shell (Zsh), Firebase, Git, Figma.

Soft Skills Time Management, Teamwork, Problem-solving.

Work Experience _____

3FORCOM - an international IT partner

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Apr 2022 - Nov 20022

Fresher Front-end Developer

• Collaborated with a four-person team to develop modern websites that fast, reliable, and maintainable.

- Designed and implemented web applications along with third-party software integrations as a web team for all interdepartmental and customer-facing projects.
- Developed cross-browser/platform HTML, CSS and JavaScript to match design specs for complex page layouts while adhering to code standards.
- Technical Skills: ReactJS, Typescript, ReduxJS, Storybooks, Bootstrap, Antd, SCSS

Tradecoin Vietnam - a crypto community

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Junior Front-end Developer

Nov 2022 - Now

- Assessed UX and UI designs for technical feasibility
- Collaborated with product team members to implement new feature developments.
- Used the best practices in NextJS to develop a dynamic site based from static image of a website design
- Performed daily operations and maintenance tasks to ensure web pages under TCVN are up-to-date and free of errors.
- Technical Skills: NextJS, Typescript, ReduxJS, CSS Module, TailwindCSS, Redis, Prisma, Web3

Projects _____

GUMAC, Vietnam

Fashion EcommerceExpand features, refine, and optimize source code.

- Implement UI from the design, discuss problems with the team to find solutions.
- Collaborated with the team leader to design cutting edge features.
- Live: GUMAC
- Technical Skills: ReactJS, ReduxJS, SASS, Storybooks, Typescript, Bootstrap.

Dalat Hasfarm Dalat Hasfarm Co., Ltd.

B2B Portal

Apr 2022 - Sept 2022

Apr 2022 - Nov 2022

- Made high quality and extendable React Components for a team leading site optimizations.
- Work to solve complex challenges with the utilization of modern web application development processes and standard methodologies.
- · Ensured the technology implemented promoted efficiency, speed, and smooth functionality.
- **Technical Skills:** ReactJS, ReduxJS, SASS, Storybooks, Typescript, Bootstrap.

TradeCoinVN Community

TradeCoinVN Corp.

Nov 2022 - Now

Crypto Community

- Build landing page project using the NextJS framework.
- Worked with teams to solve issues and find and implement efficiencies.
- Continually tested the site for usability while addressing any bugs.
- Optimize best practices for performance and SEO.
- Live: TradeCoinVN
- Technical Skills: NextJS, ReduxJS, TailwindCSS, Web3, Typescript, Redis.

APRIL 24, 2024 1

K300 Dashboard K300 Ventures

Dashboard for funding management K300 Ventures

- Build dashboard page project using the NextJS framework.
- Create APIs that are highly secure and reusable.
- Ensured the technology implemented promoted efficiency, speed, and smooth functionality.
- Technical Skills: NextJS, Prisma, TailwindCSS, NodeJS, Typescript.

Education

Can Tho University Can Tho City, Vietnam

Infomatic Applied

Aug 2017 - Feb 2020

December 2023 - Now

- Working in data labeling of Automation Driven Car
- Courses: System Management, OOP Programming, Data Structures, Graph Theory, Front-end Development

Languages_

English Limited working proficiency

Vietnamese Native proficiency

APRIL 24, 2024